2: TITLE HERE!!!
3: SAMPLE: Pro Finder: Smart shopping solution
8: A Project Portfolio in ITE322ùTechnopreneurship
9: Presented to the Faculty of College of Computer Studies
10: Mindoro State University
17: In Partial Fulfillment
18: of the Requirements for the Degree of 
19: Bachelor of Science in Information Technology
23: By
25: Name1
26: Name2
27: Name3
31: Submitted to
33: HAROLD Y. BANGALISAN
34: ITE322ùTechnopreneurship
39: July 2021
69: LOGO HERE! 
87: TABLE OF CONTENTS
89: Page
90: INTRODUCTIONààààààààààààààààààààà.  4
91: Why Profinder (sample title only).àààààààà  ààà.à.. 5
92: NAME AND DESCRIPTION OF THE PRODUCT/SERVICEà.à.  6
93: BUSINESS MODEL CANVASààààààààààààà.àà. 7
94: Value Propositionàààààààààààààààààà.à.  8
95: Customer Segmentsààààààààààààààà.ààà  8
96: Channelààààààààààààààààààààà.àà.  8
97: Relationshipààààààààààààààààààààà..   8
98: Key Partnersààààààààààààààààààààà..  8
99: Costààààààààààààààààààààààààà.  8
100: Key Resourcesààààààààààààààààà.ààà.  8
101: Manpower requirementsààààààààààà.àà.ààààà. 8
102: Organization structureààààààààààààààà.àààà.     9
103: Key Activitiesàààààààààààààààààà.ààà  9
104: Revenue Streamààààààààààààààààààà...  9
105: BROCHUREààààààààààààààààààààààà10
106: MARKET VALIDATIONàààààààààààà.àààààà11
107: FINANCIAL ASPECTààààààààààààààààààà14
108: Projected Costàààààààààààààààààààà.. 14
109: Financial Statement û Project Cash Flowààààààààà 15
110: PROTOTYPINGààààààààààààààààààààà. 16
111: PITCHING DIALOGàààààààààààààààààààà17
112: CONCLUSIONàààààààààààààààààààààà 18
113: APPENDICESàààààààà.ààààààààààààà... 19
114: REFERENCESàààààààààààààààààà.ààà.. 24
116: INTRODUCTION
118: Introduction about technology innovation, subject, and project. 
119: WHY PRO FINDER? 
121: Why stakeholder / client / target users will select your technology.
126: NAME AND DESCRIPTION OF THE PRODUCT/SERVICE
129: BUSINESS MODEL CANVAS
132: Brief description of Business model canvas and its importance. How did you do it.
134: BROCHURE
137: 		Figure description (sample only)
141: 	The figure shown the back page of the project. wherein it includes the about the project and the product overviews.
143: MARKET VALIDATION
146: Summary 
148: Summary of the conduct of market validation
151: FINANCIAL ASPECT
152: Projected Cost (Sample Only)
167: Financial Statement û Project Cash Flow (Sample only)
171: PROTOTYPING
175: Terms and Conditions
176: 	In this form, the terms and conditions are presented which are rules by which one must agree to abide in order to use the service. 
178:  Privacy Policy
179: 	This is used in order for the passenger and driverÆs information to be managed and protected by the application.  
184: Register As
186: Sign Up
187: In this form, passengers and drivers must enter their information to have an account and they must click the Terms and Conditions to finish signing up. 
198: Log-in Form
199: In order to log-in, the user must enter the email or phone number and the password. The user can also log-in using their Google account and if they forgot the password, there is a label which they can recover it.   
202: User Account
203: 	This is the form in which the passenger already have an account and is ready to book a Public Utility Vehicle anytime.

205: Menu
206: This is the Menu Form in which the passenger can see the different PUVÆs and also the passengers can also see their current location.
217: Brief description of the project prototype
219: PITCHING DIALOG
220: SAMPLE ONLY: According to Gordon Hamilton on his personal vlog, ôSupermarket shopping: one of the biggest causes of high blood pressure in modern, day to day lifeà Why do so many normal people turn in to self-centered, frenzied, selfish Neanderthals the moment they approach a supermarket?ö
221: And these are some problems we encounter when we are shopping in the supermarket.
222: did you find shopping irritating?
223: is it difficult for you to find a certain product?
224: Do the salesperson assist you to locate what you are looking?
225: do you consume lot of time in finding a certain product?
226: but why would we suffer in doing shopping when you could make it easy!
227: And nowà
228: WeÆre introducing to you PROFINDER!
229: without hassle of searching your product,
230: without the assistance of the salesperson,
231: without consuming lot of time
232: with just one type away you will be able to find your product!
233: This application can be used by all but most especially for those
234: -busy persons
235: - old buyers
236: -pwds
237: So what are you waiting for! Grab now and use it for an easy shopping!
238: ôIf you've ever walked a mile into a virgin forest - you know, like a deep forest where trees have been uncut - the energy is totally different from the shopping mall. ô
239: -James Redfield
241: CONCLUSION
242: Conclusion about the project, market validation, costumers, stakeholders, prototype.
245: APPENDICES
246: CURRICULUM VITAE
262: REFERENCES (APA Format)
264: Journals
266: à.
268: Internet Resources
270: à..
